<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Volunteers on Mrs. Martin&#39;s Website</title>
    <link>https://ittybittyteach.github.io/tags/volunteers/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Volunteers on Mrs. Martin&#39;s Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ittybittyteach.github.io/tags/volunteers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Class Field Trip to the Zoo</title>
      <link>https://ittybittyteach.github.io/posts/class-field-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ittybittyteach.github.io/posts/class-field-trip/</guid>
      <description>Need Chaperones Heading to the zoo! We&amp;rsquo;re off to the zoo this week and we need some helpers. Moms and Dads that can be of help please see the front office for the forms to volunteer. These must be turned in and cleared with the front desk by Wednesday.
At the zoo we will have a guide group and students will be paired up with parents. I will have packets for each of you who have already cleared with me and those that are still working with the office.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello Everyone!</title>
      <link>https://ittybittyteach.github.io/posts/first_blog_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ittybittyteach.github.io/posts/first_blog_post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Parents and Guardians This is where I will be posting the latest and greatest up and coming events our class will be venturing on. We will be having a lot of fun this year in the second grade. There will be so much to do and so much to learn. Your students will be involved in our Mystery Science Projects, containing vast amounts of information in the natural sciences. Your children will be exploring the fascinating world of plants, butterflies, volcanoes, geology and electricity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1</title>
      <link>https://ittybittyteach.github.io/posts/blogpost2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ittybittyteach.github.io/posts/blogpost2/</guid>
      <description>Looking for classroom helpers I am always looking for anyone who would like to help out in the classroom. Even if you like come in help organized books for an hour, any little bit is super useful. Please, send me an email with the date and times you are available.
This week will be starting off a new unit on building our own theme parks. The kids are excited to get the creative juices flowing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>